[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "What is Dart ?",
"a": "Database",
"b": "Programming Language",
"c": "Text Editor",
"d": "Browser",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "What is Widget in Flutter ?",
"a": "A part of UI",
"b": "A photo file",
"c": "A Music file",
"d": "Video",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Flutter uses",
"a": "Dart",
"b": "C++",
"c": "HTML",
"d": "python",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "AppBar is part of ?",
"a": "UI",
"b": "Image",
"c": "Music",
"d": "Video",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Fluter is used for ?",
"a": "Cooking",
"b": "Drawing",
"c": "App Development",
"d": "Browsering",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "Sized Box gives ?",
"a": "Sound",
"b": "Space",
"c": "Color",
"d": "Video",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Flutter apps run on ?",
"a": "Only Android",
"b": "Only iOS",
"c": "Both Android and iOS",
"d": "Only Window",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Main Function in Dart is ?",
"a": "main()",
"b": "start()",
"c": "run()",
"d": "begin()",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "setState() is used to ?",
"a": "Delete app",
"b": "Close app",
"c": "Update",
"d": "Restartapp",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "Flutter logo color ?",
"a": "Green",
"b": "Red",
"c": "Blue",
"d": "Yellow",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
}
]